ANOINTING WATER REVIVAL IN THE UK - DELIVERANCE CONTINUES
There is power in the name of Jesus
Lord to give up I'd be a fool
You are my all in all
Jesus Lamb of God
Worthy is Your Name
We want them to be mad!
These kids are great.
She is a seer.
Who are you, you evil spirit?
She is delivering nations, this one.
Spirit of snake.
We are spiritual snakes. We were brought into her life to destroy her destiny.
She is going to speak about the future, about the past, about the present.
You spirit of snake, what have you done to her life?
We don't want that; you know that; you know our kingdom is in danger.
Why?
How long have you been in this body?
Since birth; we knew her plan.
This woman, what is her occupation, what does she do?
She is doing nothing.
What have you done to her family, her home, her marriage?
We brought the spirit of madness; we want them to be mad.
They are great, these kids.
We have got to tempt them all - six of them.
Why?
You evil spirit, with all your evil plans for this family and for this woman...
That name is dangerous!
Which name?
She is trying to call it - no way.
That name she is trying to speak now.
Which name?
We can't say it; we are in danger!
She was given a volcanic anointing fire to burn all of us.
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Why? Don't call that name!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Please, we are dying; please don't!
Why do you not want that Name to be called?
Why do you have to call that Name? Why? Why?
In the name of Jesus Christ, come out of her, in Jesus' name!
We are dying.
Come out! You have no place in this body.
You and your nonsense plans, you are coming out, in Jesus' name.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Every chain that has been holding her destiny, let it be loosed, in Jesus' name.
Let every chain be loosed, in Jesus' name.
This is deliverance taking place in Jesus' name right now.
The evil spirit said it was a spirit of snake that had caused madness in the family.
But right now we are seeing the name of Jesus Christ taking authority over this demonic spirit,
as she is being completely set free, in Jesus' name.
You are free; rise up, in Jesus' name.
You are free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord Jesus!
ANOINTING WATER REVIVAL IN THE UK - TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Linda Nambili.
I come from Namibia and I came to visit the UK for six months.
The problems that brought me here were spiritual attacks and no progress in life.
When we were going to the prayer line, I couldn't walk.
Something was pulling me, like muscles pulling in my leg.
Before I reached there, I found that I couldn't see anyone else.
There was just darkness, and I was screaming.
From there, a voice was talking from deep within me; I couldn't control it.
It was speaking against my control.
So, you were experiencing spiritual attack, but by the grace of God you came to the Anointing Water service
and were ministered to with the Anointing Water, and Jesus Christ met you. Amen?
Amen! Hallelujah!
Now that you have received this wonderful deliverance,
we encourage you to stay close to Jesus and far from sin, so that this will remain permanent in your life.
Amen; thank You, Lord Jesus; I am free!
RV: Mel Flowers 27/03/2019